[
    {
        "front": "Test 2",
        "back": "Prueba 2",
        "timesAnswered": 0,
        "correctAnswerCount": 0,
        "winStreak": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "I want to be free",
        "back": "A Huacho me fui",
        "timesAnswered": 0,
        "correctAnswerCount": 0,
        "winStreak": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "To give, grant",
        "back": "Conceder",
        "timesAnswered": 0,
        "correctAnswerCount": 0,
        "winStreak": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "Intoxicated, drunk",
        "back": "Ebrio",
        "timesAnswered": 0,
        "correctAnswerCount": 0,
        "winStreak": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "Shoot-out",
        "back": "Balacera",
        "timesAnswered": 0,
        "correctAnswerCount": 0,
        "winStreak": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "Complain",
        "back": "Quejarse",
        "timesAnswered": 0,
        "correctAnswerCount": 0,
        "winStreak": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "Stomach",
        "back": "Barriga",
        "timesAnswered": 0,
        "correctAnswerCount": 0,
        "winStreak": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "Miserable",
        "back": "Destrozado",
        "timesAnswered": 0,
        "correctAnswerCount": 0,
        "winStreak": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "Pending 2",
        "back": "Pendiente 2",
        "timesAnswered": 0,
        "correctAnswerCount": 0,
        "winStreak": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "Pending 3",
        "back": "Pendiente 3",
        "timesAnswered": 0,
        "correctAnswerCount": 0,
        "winStreak": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "Pending 4",
        "back": "Pendiente 4",
        "timesAnswered": 0,
        "correctAnswerCount": 0,
        "winStreak": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "Pending 5",
        "back": "Pendiente 5",
        "timesAnswered": 0,
        "correctAnswerCount": 0,
        "winStreak": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "Pending 6",
        "back": "Pendiente 6",
        "timesAnswered": 0,
        "correctAnswerCount": 0,
        "winStreak": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "Pending 7",
        "back": "Pendiente 7",
        "timesAnswered": 0,
        "correctAnswerCount": 0,
        "winStreak": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "Pending 8",
        "back": "Pendiente 8",
        "timesAnswered": 0,
        "correctAnswerCount": 0,
        "winStreak": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "Pending 9",
        "back": "Pendiente 9",
        "timesAnswered": 0,
        "correctAnswerCount": 0,
        "winStreak": 0
    }
]

